Come on !
- I have gone . Now ! - Now !
Look out girls ! Here we go !
Look to the left .
- Paddle ! - Come on ! - Hold on !
- Can you see her ? - Mummy !
Look out !
Gone !
Paddle !
Look out !
Come on !
Fuck !
Hold on !
Look out !
Jesus Christ !
Gone !
Very nice !
Yes !
- Mummy ! - Hey , guys !
Oh , Jessie !
Yeah !
That was amazing .
- Oh , you girls were screaming . - Yes . - All right , Jessie ?
- It 's all right . - That wasn 't so bad , was it ?
- No , it was a piece of piss . - Yeah !
Bitch !
- Bit more , bit more . - Go on , Paul . Fish her out .
There . Got you .
- You all right ? - Yeah .
- It 's freezing . I can 't feel my fingers . - Okay .
Heave !
Okay !
Jessie , Jessie .
Ah , come here . Oh , baby !
It was just amazing .
Would you like to do that ?
Come on , Jessie , it 's freezing . Let 's go back to the car .
- Go with your Daddy . I 'll just help the girls . - All right .
It 's okay , you go on . We can finish up here .
You sure ? Thanks , guys . I 'll see you at the hotel .
- Yeah ? - See ya .
Thanks .
Jess , when we get home , shall I phone Rachel 's mum ?
See if Rachel wants to come to dinner on Thursday ?
Yeah .
Yeah ? Okay .
When she comes round , she can help us plan your birthday party .
Okay .
You gonna invite any boys this time ?
Are you okay ? You seem a bit distant .
I 'm fine .
Jess ?
Jessie !
- No ! Jessie ! - Shh !
Shh ! I 'm sorry . She 's gone .
- I 'm sorry ! - No ! No ! No !
No , no !
No , no , no !
She 's gone , Sarah .
Shh !
- No ! - Shh .
No !
I 'm sorry .
Well , it 's mud , blood and beer ...
or sweet Jesus .
It 's great . Turn that shite off .
That 's frightening .
Listen , we don 't have to do this , you know .
We can head back and stay in town .
Get wasted , go to a barn dance .
Now that is frightening .
You 're right . We don 't have to do this .
But I 'm not gonna be the one to tell Juno .
She 's a piece of work , man .
She always brings us out into the middle of ...
Well , look at it .
- She came to Scotland last year . - Yeah , and left pretty quickly .
Sarah !
- Oh-ho ! - Beth !
Juno .
You look fantastic !
- It 's great to see you ! Oh ! - Ah , come here .
Let me look at you . Wow !
Everything is gonna be fine .
Better . It 's gonna be great .
- Becca and Sam can 't wait to see you . Why don 't you go in ? - Okay .
- Give me these . Yeah ! - Yeah ? Thanks .
- Okay ? - Yeah .
Okay .
Ooh ! Very nice .
How is she ?
Well , she 's here .
One step at a time , eh ?
Hey , hey , hey ! Who are you calling a fucking cheater ?
I 'm calling you a fucking cheater .
- I 've missed you right . - Hello !
- Hey ! - Hello !
Hello .
- You do look really good . - Thank you . Sam . Yeah ! - Oh , you look amazing !
- Hey ! - Hey ! - Let me put the bags down .
- Oh ! Ah , you ! - Thank you !
- Friend ! Oh , girls so nice to see you . Uh-huh , girl friend ... - Honey , I have really got to say ...
- I 'm starving . - Okay , go . Go , go . - Thank you .
- What have you got ? - Er , well , there 's a bit of ... - Thank you .
Sam . Sam .
Thank you so much for your letter . It meant a lot to me .
Oh , Sarah , look , I 'm so sorry that I couldn 't be there . You know
mid-terms and ...
- It 's okay . - You know , Sam is gonna be Doctor Van Ney in like a year 's time .
No !
- Please tell me it 's longer than that . Shit ! - I am so proud of my little sister !
- Who wants a drink ? - Me ! Yes ! Yeah ! Me ! Me ! Yeah !
- Brandy shot ? - Yeah , yeah .
- So , Beth ... - Mm-hm ?
I hear it all starts falling apart past 25 ?
Is that what they teach you at medical school , yeah ?
- To take the piss ? - Uh-huh .
Cheeky bitch !
Can anyone make me feel any older ?
- Oh , here we go . - Hello .
- Hi , you must be the teacher . - Hi . Yeah , uh-huh , yeah . - Beth , Sarah , this is Holly .
Juno 's protégé .
Really ? I always thought Juno would eat her young .
Oh , nice !
I 'm well able to handle myself , thanks very much .
I 've heard about you . You 're that mentalist that jumps off buildings .
Ah , Base jumping . You should try it . Seriously .
- Yeah . - So you live in America now ?
Ran out of things to jump off in Galway , you know .
I 'm always searching for the next big high .
- Sure you 'd know all about that . - Sorry ?
- Oh ! - No .
Juno showed me a photo of when you used to climb together .
Oh , I found this classic picture .
- Ah ! - What 's have this ?
- Oh , no ! - Oh , my God ! - Oh , no !
- Oh , no ! - Look at the state of us ! Oh , my God . That 's bad .
Sexy !
Love each day .
Used to be something Paul used to say .
Anyway ... cheers .
- Here 's to our adventure . - Skoal , skoal .
- To us ! - Skoal ! Skoal ! Now . - Cheers ! Cheers !
Come on , light , you bastard !
So , have you done Boreham Caverns before ?
I saw it in a book once . It 's for tourists . It 's not adventure .
Might as well have hand rails and a fucking gift shop .
If you 're a caver , jumper , climber
you just do it and not give a shite .
Or the thing that 's bigger than you will get you .
You want adventure , Holly ?
When have I ever let you down ?
- It 's breathing ? - What ?
Nothing .
Holly , tomorrow 's gonna be awesome . Okay ?
Yeah .
Take this .
You need it .
What about Josh , Sam ? Are you guys still together ?
Kind of . Sort of .
Different
shifts .
Oh , my God .
Oh , my Jesus !
What do you think , eh ?
Don 't say a fucking word , all right ?
It was a Christmas present ! Okay ?
All right , shut up .
- What about you Holly ? Got a man ? - Oh ...
I 'm a sports fuck like Juno .
- What ? - Rebecca , too , I think .
But when I 'm older , I want to have lots of babies .
Beth , did Sarah tell you that
Rebecca and I go into business together ?
Wakey !
Wakey .
I feel like roadkill .
Give me five minutes .
Five minutes .
Good morning , my little ones !
Wakey , wakey !
God morgon ! ( In Swedish ) Good morning !
Is that what you call it ? It 's fucking freezing !
Holly !
We 're leaving at seven . Don 't be late .
Try that .
The queen is dead .
Long live ...
the fucking queen !
Beth , you 're not driving .
- If you drive we 'll never get there . What ? - Come on ? All right ! Paper , scissors , stone .
- Come on . - Oh , you 're a dick .
- Go on . - Okay .
- There you go . - No , wait , babe . Best of three .
- How is best of three ? - Nope ! Best of three ! - I 'll drive .
Right , ladies . Group photo .
Okay . You 'd better hurry it up . We 're running late .
- I look like shit . - We all look like shit .
- Now just give me a smile . - Okay ! Yeah .
- Hat ? No hat ? - No , no hat . - Shit ! - Thanks !
- No hat , no hat . - All right !
- Yeah . - Yeah . - Run , run , run , run .
- Say " sausage " ! - Sausage !
Sarah , slow down a bit .
- I 'm having fun ! - She 's having fun .
Whoa ! Whoa ! Turn , turn , turn there .
Let 's off road !
Great !
You should have some water .
Trying to set this watch is impossible . The buttons are too fucking small .
- Leave it alone . - Why do you wear it , anyway ?
My boyfriend gave it to me . It 's sentimental .
It 's fucking mental .
Any guy that gave that to me I 'd dump him on the spot .
Juno , are you sure we 're going the right way ?
Relax , I 've never been lost in my life .
Marvellous .
So have you done these caves before ?
No . But they are only level two . Quite safe , don 't worry .
- I wasn 't . - The only danger is that I might fall asleep .
Boreham Caves . More like boredom caves .
- Nice parking . - Thanks .
This one time in Galway .
When I free-climbed the cathedral ,
a priest chased me down the whole for half a mile .
That was brilliant !
- I shouldn 't have wasted the effort , though . The best of all follow-up . - Holly , shut up !
Rebecca , leave her alone .
- It it 's story , Holly . - Okay , guys , let 's get moving . We 're running late .
- Come on , keep up . - I have !
- Jesus . - Hey , Holly , wait up .
- Move it , short arse ! - Jesus .
Hey , hey .
- Oi , Carter , get to the back now . - Come on , you lazy bastard !
You finally caught up with me .
Juno , ...
are we there yet ?
There 's a river about half a mile ahead .
When we reach it , we follow it up to the mouth of the cave . Okay ?
How does she know there 's a river up ahead ?
I can 't hear a thing .
She can probably smell it .
She came up here last week to check the route out .
It 's rule number one :
File a flight plan and stick to it .
- And rule number two ? - Don 't go wandering off .
You think it 's dark when you turn out the lights . Well , down there it 's pitch black .
You can get dehydration ,
- disorientation ... - Yeah , yeah , yeah .
- ... claustrophobia , panic attacks ... - Blah , blah , blah .
... paranoia ,
... hallucinations ,
... visual and aural deterioration
a cave can collapsed ,
... you can drown ,
... if you breathing gets ...
Hey !
Yeah , lovely , Holly .
A real Kodak moment .
Don 't touch it !
You wouldn 't want to piss it off .
What do you think did that , Sam ? A bear ?
What is this , Nature Detectives ?
- It could have been Big Foot for all you know . Come on . - Sam , stop poking it with a fucking stick , let 's go .
This is it .
You 're having a laugh !
Afraid not .
I 'm an English teacher , not fucking Tomb Raider .
You 'll be fine .
Okay , Sarah , Beth , you 're up next .
- Sam , stay with Becca . - Okay .
Do what she does , and you 'll be fine .
Holly , safety first ! I don 't want any stunts this time .
- You okay ? See you down there . - No .
Hey you , make sure your cow 's tail is locked
there and there . You hold on to this like that .
Look , you know , I have done this before , you know ?
- I 'm only looking after you . - And I appreciate it , in small doses .
You gotta see this place !
It 's beautiful !
You won 't believe this , Beth .
Oh , shit ! Oh , shit ! shit , shit , shit .
Oh , my God ! I 'm gonna die .
Ah , piece of piss .
Oh , my God !
It 's incredible .
Clear !
- It 's Holly ! - Shit ! Move !
Holly , ...
you do this safely , in order , following my lead .
Okay ?
Take it slow and easy .
Juno .
Smart arse .
- It 's okay . It 's okay . It 's okay ! - Stop !
- They 're gone . They 're gone now . Look . - Oh , God . No .
One bat , two bats !
Fifty bats !
Holly , ...
fuck off .
Which way ?
There 's only one way out of this chamber , and that 's down the pipe .
Okay .
It 's a drop .
- Okay ? - Yeah .
Holly , chuck us your bag .
Wow !
Oh , my God !
- It 's amazing ! - It 's Christ !
Hey !
- Find anything good ? - Jesus Christ !
Come on , let 's eat .
Holly , would you take a break ?
It 's want to take a few more shots .
This cave is a lot cooler than I thought .
Hey .
Not hungry .
You okay ?
Juno , I won 't break . I 'm fine .
- I asked you for this . - I know .
Um ...
Sarah ?
I haven 't had a chance to say that I 'm ...
really sorry I didn 't stay around longer after the accident .
Anyway
we 're all here for you now , okay ?
Yeah .
Look , sorry . I 'm feeling a bit out of it . It 's probably jet lag or something .
So I 'm just gonna take a look around . Okay ?
Yeah , okay .
Why don 't you try and find us the way through , huh ?
Hey , don 't go too far .
What 's up with her ? She looks like she 's seen a ghost or something .
She 's fine .
Hey .
I 've found the next passage !
- That 's it ? It 's a bit small , isn 't it ? - Hey , hey , hey !
I don 't ... I don 't get this .
What ?
This is not how I imagined it from reading the book .
That 's why I don 't trust books .
Leaves too much room for interpretation .
Something wrong ?
- No . - No , it 's nothing .
I 'm taking point , guys .
- Oh , my God . - Careful .
Just find the way through . We 'll wait here .
What the ...
Okay , I 'm through .
Jesus .
It 's okay .
Sarah ?
- Shit . - Are you still behind me ?
Yes .
Shit !
- Shit ! - Sarah !
- Guys , it 's Sarah . I think she might be stuck . - Shit !
I am stuck !
All right , Sarah . Calm down , just relax .
I can 't fucking relax .
Fuck ! Fuck !
OK , Sarah , you have to calm down .
And the only way you 're gonna do that is to breathe . Yeah ?
Okay , breathe slowly .
Just keep breathing .
Oh , fuck it me !
I can 't . I am dying !
- I can 't fucking breathe . Fuck ! Jesus ! - Sarah , okay , listen to me .
Just listen to my voice , yeah ?
Sarah , I 'm coming . I 'm coming back .
Okay ? Okay .
Sarah , ...
okay ?
Listen to me , keep breathing .
Okay ? Hey .
Hey , hey !
Okay .
Okay . Okay .
Look here at me , Sarah . Hey ?
Help me .
- What are you so worried about , Sarah ? Look at me . - Beth ... Jesus ! Help me .
Okay , breathe .
Breathe , okay ? Hey !
Hey , hey . Listen to me .
Listen to me .
- What are you afraid of ? What are you so afraid of ? - I can 't fucking move !
You can move !
Sarah , look at me , look at me .
Listen , the worst thing that could have happened to you has already happened .
Okay ? And you 're still here .
This is just a poxy cave .
And there 's nothing left to be afraid of . I promise .
Okay ? Okay ?
Hey ? Hey , listen . Listen . Listen to me .
You 'll love this one . You 'll love this one ! " How do you give a lemon an orgasm ? "
Goddamn it , let me hear you say it . " How do you give a lemon an orgasm ? "
- What do you do it ? You tickle its citrus ! - Tickle its citrus .
Okay , that 's better . Come on .
Okay , okay .
All right , we 're gonna move now . Take hold of my arm , all right ?
We 're gonna move slowly . That 's it , grab my arm . Okay .
Okay , come on .
Just slowly . Pull on me , okay ?
Okay . Okay .
- The rope bag . I forgot the rope bag . - Okay .
Okay .
Okay , fuck the rope bag . Okay , move !
Now ! Now !
Hold on !
Now ! Come on !
Come on , Sarah , keep hold of move !
Move !
Oh , fuck !
Come on now ! Move !
Sarah ?
- Are you okay ? - Are you okay ? All right . - I 'm all right .
Is everybody okay ?
- Don 't fucking touch me ! I 'm fine . - Becca ?
I 'm here , I 'm okay . Okay , Beth , are you injured ?
- No , I 'm fine . - Yeah ?
Nobody move until the dust has settled .
Oh , don 't worry , Juno , we 're not going anywhere .
Oh , fuck !
You might be right about that .
Jesus .
- Oh , fuck . - So what 's the story now ?
According to the guidebook , this cave system has three ways in and out .
- Secured ?
This is just one of them . Isn 't that right , Juno ?
Juno , that 's right , isn 't it ?
Check the book !
I didn 't bring it .
What ?
No point .
For Christ 's sake , Juno !
I knew it . I knew this wasn 't right !
You filed a flight plan to mountain rescue .
If we don 't report in , they 'll come looking for us .
That 's how it 's supposed to work . Except ...
I put in a flight plan for Boreham Caverns
and this isn 't Boreham Caverns , is it , Juno ?
We 're in the wrong fucking cave ?
Holly was right ! Boreham Caverns was a tourist trap !
- I ... - Don 't try and pin this fucking shite on me !
This is not caving . This is an ego trip .
Come on , Rebecca , I didn 't know this was gonna happen .
This is exactly what we believe in .
We 've always said , if there 's no risk , what 's the point ?
Don 't try and justify this .
Where ... Where are we ?
It hasn 't got a name . It 's a new system .
I wanted us all to discover it !
- No-one 's ever been down here before . - You 're fucking kidding me .
Oh , God !
- How the hell are we supposed to get out ? - There may not be a way out .
Look , there 's no going back now .
We have to find a way out of this chamber and keep pushing forward .
What the fuck do you think you 're doing ?
We all trusted you . You told me this was gonna be good for Sarah .
Have you any idea what she 's been through ?
No . Cos you couldn 't get away fast enough , you selfish cow !
You know what , Beth ?
We all lost something in that crash .
Just get us out of here .
Look , cave systems sometimes break ground .
It 's a small chance .
But if we stay here , we 'll die !
Let 's go .
- Wait ! - What ?
Don 't move , Sam !
Just don 't move !
Stay right there !
Oh , shit . No more .
Thanks , Beth .
Now I know how far down it is .
So , what now ?
One of us has to get all the way across there
so they can rig a line for you guys .
I have three cams . I need at least three more .
Where 's the other rope bag ?
Where is it ?
We lost it , when the cave collapsed .
Sorry .
Shit .
Moment , moment .
Okay . All right .
Okay .
Oh , now .
Fuck !
- Come on ! - Come on , Becca .
Do that !
You got it !
Come on , come on , come on , come on , come on , come on , come on .
Come on , Rebecca !
What are you waiting for ?
- What the ... fuck ? - You okay ?
What 's wrong ?
It 's nothing .
I 'm all right .
Okay .
Fuck !
All right , more slack .
More slack , thanks .
Fuck !
Come on . Fuck !
Okay .
Well done !
Throw me the right rope .
Okay .
Come on .
Yeah !
Now , you make it look easy .
Yeah , well , you make it look hard .
Okay .
Don 't look down , Beth ! Keep going !
- Just keep going ! - You 're okay . You 're safe .
Good .
- There you go . - Yeah .
Was this about me or you ?
It 's about us .
Getting back to what we used to be .
I wanted us to claim this place . Name it .
I thought maybe your name .
Or maybe yours .
You 're doing well . Come on .
Come on .
- All right . - There you are .
Give me your hand .
- All right . - Okay .
Yeah .
Juno ?
We 'll need everything we 've got .
Haul it in .
Fuck !
Yeah !
Reach !
Reach out !
God ! God !
Juno !
No !
Juno , it 's okay . We 've got you .
Okay , pull !
- Sam ! - Let me pass , Holly , let me pass . - Jesus !
Rebecca , show me your hand .
Jesus !
All right .
Oh , fuck !
Yes , yes , yes .
Let 's . Let go , let go .
What does it mean ?
It means we 're not the first .
- Press on mine . - It 's a piton , right ?
If there cavers down here before , surely there 's a better chance of us getting out .
This equipment is at least hundred years old .
No-one uses stuff like this anymore .
Besides , if anyone had been down here and made it out ,
- they would have named it already . - Okay . Fuck !
Becca , are you okay ?
I 'll live .
Okay .
Holly , how does it look ?
It 's tight again , but I can get through .
Okay , keep going . We 'll be right behind you .
All right .
Hey , there 's something down here .
Guys , it 's amazing .
But the batteries on our lights will run out .
- So I suggest we keep moving . - Wait a minute . Wait !
What is it , Beth ?
Juno , light up one of your flares .
- Beth , we don 't have time for this . - Just light a flare .
Really lovely , Beth , but it 's fucking useless .
No , look at it . What do you see ?
You 've got the mountain , the cave ...
and there 's two entrances .
You are a fucking genius !
I have my moments .
This means there 's another way out ?
Let 's find out .
Come on !
- Bastard ! - Which way ?
Holly , give me your lighter .
- Come on . - Here .
Fuck !
Come on ! Come on ! Shit !
That one ! Hey !
Holly !
Holly , slow down !
Careful !
Daylight ! I can see daylight !
Holly !
Careful ! Slow down !
Holly , it 's not daylight !
Holly !
Get .
- Help me ! - Hold on !
Guys !
Holly !
Sam , get down here !
Answer me !
Oh , fuck .
Think I hurt my leg !
Don 't move ! We 're coming down to you .
Oh , fuck !
No ! Fuck !
Someone better get down here !
- Oh , that 's fucking disgusting ! - Beth ! Not here , not now !
We need help ! Everybody grab a corner . We need to move her out of the water .
Nice and easy now .
And ...
Lift !
Oh , no !
- You fuckers ! - Juno , hold her down !
Find something to make me a splint out of . Beth !
- Okay , I 've got her . - Juno , use one of the ice axes .
You 'll be all right , sweetheart .
- No ! - Get hurt .
- Juno ? - Me cut !
Shit !
Be all right . Be all right . Oh , my God .
Okay .
- Sarah ! - Juno , I 'm gonna need your help here .
- Sarah ! - Juno ! - Can 't see it .
- Leave me now ! Leave me ... alone ! Leave me alone ! - Take hold of her arm . You 're gonna have to hold her down .
- What are you gonna do ? - Now don 't shake , shitty !
I need to dress the wound and rig up a splint , but I can 't while the bone is protruding .
I need to push it back in .
- Juno . - I ... hate you . - I know .
Do it .
- Bite down on this . - Peace .
- Keep hold of her . And ... - Agony ? - Just fucking bite down , okay ?
Go !
I give it stint !
Come on !
Just keep biting down , baby .
- Hold on , we 're with you , Holly ! - Jesus God ! - Bit more !
Okay . Someone give me a medical kit .
God .
Okay , okay , okay . Calm down , calm down . It 'll be all right .
- Sarah ? - Fuck !
- What are you doing ? What ? What ? - I just saw something ahead in the tunnel .
Have a look .
Sarah , ...
I promise you , I 'm gonna get you outta here .
But I can 't do it unless you 're with me .
Sarah ?
Sarah !
Sarah , look at me .
There 's nothing there .
That 's the best I can do .
- Coal miners be here .
It 'll hurt like hell and you won 't be able to put any weight on it , but at least you can move .
They combed these mountains over the centuries ago .
Anyone trapped down here be a skeleton by now .
- That is just what it looked like . Beth ! - What , what looked like ?
- Sarah thinks she saw someone back there . - Saw what ?
I don 't think I saw someone , I saw someone .
- No . You heard something and saw what you wanted to see . - What ?
- It 's the dark . It plays tricks on people . - No .
I can describe to you exactly what I saw .
What did you see ?
A man . I saw a man .
- Are ... Are you sure ? - Yes !
And it 's not the first time . I thought I saw someone before , but now I 'm sure .
Look . If there is somebody down here , then maybe they can help get us out .
- Sarah , there 's no-one down here . Forget about it ! - So say ...
Hey , hey ! We have to get Holly out of here .
Okay ? This is all that matters right now .
- Beth ! - Sam , what we do ? - It 's okay .
Is it ?
Fuck !
- Fuck it me . - Holly , you 've got to keep warm .
Got to keep warm .
Why are we walking away ? There was daylight back there .
It wasn 't daylight . It was phosphorus in the rock .
We 're two miles underground . The only light down here is ours .
Well , it looked like fucking daylight to me .
Right tunnel !
Come on . I got you .
Okay ?
Hey .
Shit .
- Shit . - Come on .
Okay .
Yeah , yeah . All right . Go !
- Shit . - Yeah . Yeah .
Come on . Come on .
Okay .
Okay . All right .
Yeah !
All right . Okay .
Jesus !
What is this place ?
Holly , ...
where 's the infrared button ?
Dead animals !
Hundreds of them !
This is not good , guys .
- Can we get out of here ? - It 's where ? - Which way ?
Come on .
- I don 't know . - What do you mean , you don 't know ?
There 's no breeze ! It could be any one of these tunnels !
- Take your pick ! - Oh , no ! Oh , anything then ?
Oh , fuck it !
Hello !
- Becca , please ! - Is there anybody there ?
Oh , there 's nothing . Hello !
- Please ! Oh , my God ! - Jeez !
It 's there ! It 's up there ! There ! There on the roof !
Look it up ?
- Yeah , but we saw his ass ! Jesus ! - It 's okay . Okay .
- Fuck it ! Did you see ... ? - What was that ? What the fuck was that ?
- I don 't know . - I don 't know ! It moved so fast , I could barely see it !
- I 've never seen anyone climb like that before ! - I told you I saw someone !
- That was not a human being ! - Don 't worry about it . - Screw this !
- Be all right . Be all right . - Let 's take our chances and pick a tunnel .
Move !
- Oh , fuck ! Fuck . - No ! No ! Fuck !
- Oh , no . - Oh , no !
What 's happening ?
Oh , shit !
It 's circling us .
Where is it ?
This way ! Move !
- Holly ! - Now ! - We 've got to move . We 've got to move .
- Let 's go ! Let 's go ! Move it ! - Come on ! Come on !
Come on !
Come on , Holly !
Move it ! Let 's go !
- Juno , the flare ! Get rid of it ! - What ? Fuck ! - All right , don 't stop ! Come on , Rebecca !
Holly , keep moving . Come on !
Holly !
Sarah !
Oh , my God ! Holly !
Get it up !
Sarah ! God !
Sarah , run !
Run !
Sarah !
Get off ! Get off ! Get off !
Fuck off !
Fucker !
Get off !
Get away , you fucker !
Holly !
No !
No ! Get off !
Get off !
Stop !
Fuck !
Fucker !
Get off !
Don 't leave me .
So , stop .
- Stop . - Oh , fuck . My battery 's gone dead .
Where are they ?
What 's happened to the others ?
Becca ... Becca , please say we 're gonna make get out of here .
Shh . Shh .
Okay .
- Okay . - Okay .
- Okay . All right . - It 's okay .
Okay .
All right . Go .
Go !
Okay .
Mummy .
If you 're really ready ...
What that ? Where we go ?
Oh , fuck ! Fuck !
No !
Go .
Quick ! Go ! Go !
All right .
Turn the light off .
A quiet .
Sarah !
Okay .
It can 't see us .
Oh , shit !
- Shit ! - Fuck !
Oh , fuck ! Oh , shit !
Becca ?
Sam ?
Becca !
Sam !
- Becca ! Becca ! - It 's Juno .
The noise she 's making , she 'll bring every one of those things down on her head .
- As long as it 's not on mine . - Sarah !
Becca !
- Shit . - Becca !
Sam !
Fuck .
Becca !
Anyone ?
Sam !
I 'm sorry , I 'm sorry .
I 'm sorry .
All right .
I know .
Fuck !
Oh , Fuck !
Fuck .
Okay .
It 's all clear .
All right .
Yeah .
Sam , run !
Now !
Go off !
Get off !
No !
No ! Get off !
We heard you crying for Sarah .
Oh , God . Oh , my God !
Where are the others ?
They ... They took Holly .
Beth ...
Beth 's dead .
Sam ,
what is that thing ?
I don 't know .
Well , it does look human .
Come ! We need to find the way out before those things find us .
No .
Sam , ...
tell us what we 're fighting .
Well ,
they 're totally blind .
And judging from what we 've seen ,
I 'd say they use sound to hunt with .
Like a bat .
And they 've evolved perfectly to live down here in the dark .
- Who is it ? - Whatever they are ,
they go to the surface to hunt .
And they bring their food back down here to eat , through an entrance .
Listen ,
if we can stay quiet enough
and evade these fuckers
I think I found the way out .
What ? You think ?
The climbing gear we found ...
whoever brought that down here marked their route .
I found those markings .
Well , what are we waiting for ?
Sarah .
I 'm not leaving without Sarah .
Sarah !
Oh , God . Fuck !
Oh , fuck !
Oh , God !
No !
Sarah , run , run !
- I 'm getting you out of here . - No !
Oh , my God !
Don 't touch me . Don 't touch me .
I heard Juno calling me . I 'm gonna go and find her .
And we 're gonna come back , and we 're gonna get you out .
No . Stay away from her .
- What ? - She did this to me .
What ?
She left me .
No , she didn 't . No . Shh .
Sarah ...
What ?
Don 't trust her .
You find your own way out .
It 's okay . It 's all right .
I 'm not gonna leave you , Beth . I 'm not gonna leave you .
- I 'm not leaving you here . Okay ? - No !
Come here .
Beth !
This is Juno 's .
It 's from Paul .
Oh , no .
Sorry .
Please !
Please ! Oh , that 's them ! Fuck !
Come please ! Come please !
Come please ! Beth .
Sarah ,
don 't leave me like this .
No , please don 't ask me to do that .
- Please . - I can 't . I can 't do that .
I can 't do that !
Please .
Okay . Shh .
Close your eyes .
No !
- No ! - Hurry !
- Go ! - Move it !
No . No .
Sarah ?
S ... Sarah ?
Look , she 's dead , Juno !
We can 't wait for her !
Come on !
- Sarah ! - Runway back !
Sarah !
Sam , come back !
Sarah ?
Run !
Oh , fuck !
Fuck !
- Come on ! - Juno , stop her ! I 'll be right behind you !
Come on .
Sam !
What are you doing ?
Come back !
Becca !
You haven 't got enough rope !
Sam !
Turn around !
- What are you doing ? Turn around ! - Sam , baby ! Sam , baby !
- Sam ! - Sam !
Sam , turn around . You can come back .
Please , baby , listen to me .
Please !
No ! No !
Sam !
No !
What are you doing ?
No ! Sam !
No !
- Sam ! - No !
Oh , no !
- Oh , no ! - No ! No !
No !
- No ! Becca ! No ! - No !
- No ! No ! - No !
Becca !
Oh , God !
Oh , God .
Okay .
What happened to you ?
Rebecca ?
No .
What about Beth ?
The sorry .
Didn 't make it .
You saw her die ?
Know .
Come on .
All right .
Come on . Come on .
All right !
No !
No ! Shit !
Sarah !
Move it !
Fuck ! Fuck !
Fuck !
Oh , God ! Oh , God ! Oh , God ! Oh , yeah !
Yeah .
Mummy ?
{ \ move ( 400,10,190,270,100,400 ) \ fad ( 0,1000 ) \ fscx80 \ fscy80 \ t ( 0,6000 , \ fscx125 \ fscy125 ) \ cH000000 \ 3cH00FFFF } Subtitles by [ Man / From / Beyond ] 78